export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: 'All I ask in return is that you ______ to me.',
        optionA: 'have been listening',
        optionB: 'listen',
        optionC: 'are listening',
        optionD: 'have listened',
        answer: 'B',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'Sue is allergic ____ peanuts.',
        optionA: 'to',
        optionB: 'for',
        optionC: 'with',
        optionD: 'in',
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'Bob decided to buy 50  ______ to add to his ranch.',
        optionA: 'ox',
        optionB: 'oxies',
        optionC: 'oxes',
        optionD: 'oxen',
        answer: 'D',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'I  ______ book you might like.',
        optionA: 'came up with',
        optionB: 'came out',
        optionC: 'came across',
        optionD: 'came along',
        answer: 'C',
    },    
    {
        prompt: 'Have you been  in contact  ____ your old school mates?',
        optionA: 'with',
        optionB: 'in',
        optionC: 'of',
        optionD: 'about',
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'I  _________  my therapist next week.',
        optionA: 'have seen',
        optionB: 'am seeing',
        optionC: 'saw',
        optionD: 'see',
        answer: 'B',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'Brooke  _________ on my nerves!',
        optionA: 'gets always',
        optionB: 'had got',
        optionC: 'always is getting',
        optionD: 'is always getting',
        answer: 'D',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'The questions were  _______ easy!',
        optionA: 'such',
        optionB: 'a very so',
        optionC: 'so very',
        optionD: 'such a',
        answer: 'C',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'We  _______ the fence _______ tomorrow.',
        optionA: 'are … painting',
        optionB: 'are having … painted',
        optionC: 'had … had',
        optionD: 'are having … paint',
        answer: 'B',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'I wish you  _______ making assumptions about me!',
        optionA: 'would stop',
        optionB: 'stop',
        optionC: 'will stop',
        optionD: 'have had stopped',
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'If we are going to expand, we will need to find an___ to back up our project.',
        optionA: 'investor',
        optionB: 'investment',
        optionC: 'invested',
        optionD: 'invester',
        answer: 'A',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'Her children are two adorable  ________ girls.',
        optionA: 'six years old',
        optionB: 'six years of age',
        optionC: 'six-years-old',
        optionD: 'six-year-old',
        answer: 'D',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'You  _______ put this much salt in the pot!',
        optionA: 'ought not',
        optionB: 'ought to not',
        optionC: 'ought not to',
        optionD: "oughtn't to",
        answer: 'C',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'Snow _____ the ball to Ingman, and he scores!',
        optionA: 'has passed',
        optionB: 'passed',
        optionC: 'is passing',
        optionD: "passes",
        answer: 'D',
    },
    {
        prompt: 'The boat _____ in 2 hours! Hurry!',
        optionA: 'leaves',
        optionB: 'is leaving',
        optionC: 'will leave',
        optionD: "has left",
        answer: 'A',
    },



]